This is the world of the Beyonders.
By drinking potions. humans are able to attain
various powers of the Beyonders
and ascend to divinity.
The 22 Pathways begin with
the weakest. Sequence 9.
The lower the sequence number.
the stronger the Beyonder's abilities.
Strong Beyonders of the higher-level Sequences
can wield powers strong enough to rival gods.
This path of evolution is called
the Path of the Divine.
Fifth Epoch. the Iron Age
September 9th. 1349
TINGEN CITY   DOOMSDAY
The world is a falsehood.
Chaos is constant and eternal.
The Supreme Being bestows blessings
through depravity.
filth.
and darkness.
Faint struggles end in futility.
never to awaken.
Carrying the sin of blasphemy.
the shepherd crawls with devotion.
I shall offer you all of the sacrificial lambs.
in order to welcome...
your divine descent!
It hurts.
Two Months Prior
Fifth Epoch. the Iron Age
June 28th. 1349
Where am I?
A nightmare?
A gun!
It hurts!
It's not a brain hemorrhage. is it?
Or sudden death from fatigue?
Klein.
Who's there?!
Who is Klein?
This isn't me.
"Klein"?
I've...
transmigrated?
Situation report.
Yes. Captain.
Two deceased.
Welch and Naya.
history graduates from Khoy University.
Judging from the scene. it was suicide.
but Black Divination was likely performed here.
or perhaps a Beyonder was sacrificed.
As a result. some kind of evil power
has descended here.
This individual is...?
Klein Moretti.
A classmate of the deceased.
Both his parents are deceased.
and he currently lives with his siblings.
Klein Moretti.
A citizen of Tingen City of Awwa County
in the Loen Kingdom
of the Northern Continent.
A fresh history graduate.
Proficient in ancient Feysac and Hermes.
May 29th. Welch came to see me.
He claimed to have come across
an ancient notebook.
June 20th.
we deciphered the first page.
My Goddess!
This is a notebook from the Fourth Epoch!
The writer hailed from...
The Antigonus Family.
June 21st. 22nd. 25th.
Antigonus.
The Black Emperor.
The Tudor Empire.
The summit of the Hornacis Mountain Range.
June 26th.
"Are all these strange things real?"
It's now the 28th.
Why is there no entry from the 27th?
Hermes language?
"Everyone will die.
including me."
Why would Klein write that?
What did he encounter?
Brother?
Melissa Moretti. Younger Sister of Klein
Tingen Technical School Student
You stayed up all night reading again?
What are you doing?
I just woke up. I'm cleaning up a bit.
You're acting secretive.
What was that?
This... seems to be...
broken again.
What's with that look of
disparagement and resignation?
Doesn't pulling the button up adjust the time?
It's okay now.
What is that expression?
The look of someone caring
for her idiot brother?
The wound's almost healed up.
A healing effect from transmigrating?
A gunshot right through the temple?
Was it suicide?
Or was it disguised as suicide?
Although Klein's remaining
memories are scattered
and many important details are missing.
I can be certain
that whatever is happening has
to do with that ancient notebook.
Then... what about my transmigration?
Everything had been normal lately.
I had just been down on my luck
with work. That's all.
Wait. that's right!
I did a luck enhancement ritual
just before dinner!
Klein.
Go back to bed if you're still feeling out of it.
I'm all right.
All right. then. I'm off to school.
Remember to buy eight pounds of fresh bread.
It spoils quickly in this heat.
Oh. and buy some mutton and peas. too.
You've been working hard on your job search.
I'll make you mutton stewed with peas.
I'll be coming home a bit late today.
Wait for me. okay?
I'm sorry. Melissa.
I might not be here when you get back.
A revolver is nowhere near quiet.
and yet Melissa didn't notice
a thing from the next room.
The longer I stay here.
the more dangerous it becomes.
I'd best try that luck enhancement ritual again.
Maybe I'll be able to transmigrate back.
I hope I'll get to eat dinner at home today.
Mrs. Smyrin. eight pounds of rye bread.
Klein. you've graduated now. haven't you?
All thanks to your well wishes. Mrs. Smyrin.
What an fine young lad you are.
I'm sure you'll be able to make good money
and move into a new place in no time.
You and your siblings shouldn't have
to live in an apartment like that.
You should at least have your own... bathroom.
Mrs. Smyrin.
you sure sound like a young. energetic lady today.
Goodbye. Mrs. Smyrin.
Goodbye. young Klein.
Iron Cross Street
Tingen City. Loen Kingdom
The sun looks about the same.
If not for the eerie crimson moon.
this would be just like a parallel Earth.
Threes.
Tens!
Jacks.
Pass.
Fighting the Landlord?
Oh. that's right.
That game exists in this world. too.
I think it was...
about 100 years ago when the Intis Emperor.
Roselle Poetry Collection
Roselle Gustav. invented it.
He also invented tarot divination
and the steam engine.
as well as improving the sailing boat
and promoting the Spring Festival tradition.
If we followed novel logic.
then could Emperor Roselle Gustav...
have been a transmigrator?
Maybe even a fellow countryman?
A circus performance?
Sir. tonight at seven o'clock!
We await your presence.
Praise the Goddess.
Lost sheep.
come forth.
Accept this guidance for your path ahead.
Regence
Where did he go?
Destiny is profound. its path unpredictable.
Tarot can help you...
peek into its mysteries.
Tarot?
Those are just like the tarot cards on Earth.
Emperor Roselle really was a transmigrator. then?
You're the first person to seek divination today.
It's on the house.
Have a seat.
It's free?
Indeed.
Now. let's begin.
Wait.
Let me ask one more thing.
What about interpreting
the cards. then? Also free?
Th-That's... also free.
They say there's nothing more
expensive than something free.
What would you like to read?
Past.
present.
and future.
Please shuffle the cards
and focus your mind on that which you seek.
I've already done so.
Please start.
This represents your past.
This. your present.
And this. your future.
All right. Mr. Free.
Which card do you want to see first?
The present.
The Fool.
The Fool?
The "0" card of the tarot?
A fresh beginning with
all kinds of possibilities?
Hey!
Why are you impersonating me again?!
You're just an animal trainer.
and don't you forget it!
Well. then.
Is an animal trainer who doesn't want
to be a fortune-teller a bad clown?
Go check on your baboons.
Don't let me catch you again!
Sir. my divination and interpretation
has been quite accurate...
The Seven Orthodox Gods of the North Continent
The Eternal Blazing Sun. the Lord of Storms.
the God of Wisdom and Knowledge.
the Evernight Goddess. the Earth Mother.
the God of Combat. and the God of Steam
and Machinery are the seven orthodox gods
recognized by the various countries across the
North Continent during the Fifth Epoch.
Their forms are not known.
and they are represented only by symbols.
The Celestial Worthy of Heaven and Earth
Be this a luck enhancement ritual
or a transmigration ritual...
Please. just send me home.
Place the four portions of staple food
in the four corners of the room.
Stand in the center of the room.
Take four steps counter-clockwise
in the shape of a square.
The Immortal Lord of Heaven and Earth for Blessings.
The Sky Lord of Heaven and Earth for Blessings.
The Exalted Thearch of Heaven and Earth for Blessings.
The Celestial Worthy of Heaven and Earth for Blessings!
Awwa County Police
Nothing happened?
That can't be right.
Just now. it—
You wouldn't die if you didn't court death.
The Celestial Worthy of Heaven and Earth
What... is this place?
Mirror. mirror...
In the name of the Hall family.
I command you... to awaken!
Sir...
If I may ask... Where is this?
Did I...
summon these two?
If I may ask...
Might you be the master of this Divine Realm?
"Divine Realm"?
A place without so much as a shrine.
and you call it a Divine Realm?
Is this what people call "the law
follows the word"? Materialization?
Could it be that this gray fog...
is something like a third-party tool for my use?
It is!
Sir.
If I may ask...
What is this place?
And who are you?
Me?
Am I Zhou Mingrui?
Or am I Klein?
You may address me as...
The Fool.
The Fool?
Mr. Fool.
what is it that you are doing?
A test run.
A test run?
Mr. Fool. is the test over?
Might you permit our return?
Certainly.
If you make a formal request.
you can return this very moment.
From her voice. she seems
to be an innocent young girl.
As for the other.
he sounds calm and cautious—
difficult to get a grasp on.
This is such a wonderful experience.
I've always hoped for something
mysterious and supernatural to occur.
Mr. Fool. what can I do to become a Beyonder?
A Beyonder?
I've never even heard of such a thing.
This gentleman here should be able
to answer your question.
The lady across from me has the
manner of speech of a Loen noble.
while I'm far away. by the Sonia Sea.
Between us lies a great distance.
How did The Fool manifest this?
You are from Loen. correct?
To become a Beyonder. join the
organization of the Evernight Goddess.
the Lord of Storms. or some other.
Though the majority of us will not meet
a Beyonder once in our entire lives.
it is indisputable that they exist.
Even now. they fight against
the dangers that grow in the dark.
But... I don't want to lose my freedom.
Then you can only seek the royal families
or the noble families over a millennium old.
Are there no other options?
I do have...
two sets of Sequence 9 potion formulas.
"Sequence 9"?
Really? Which two sets?
One is named "Sailor."
and the other is "Spectator."
You'll have acute powers of observation.
and will be able to judge "actors"
in the secular world.
It seems they're referring to various
kinds of superhuman powers.
"Sequence 9" sounds like a power level.
I think I have fallen in love with
this feeling of being a "Spectator"...
This gray fog and my transmigration...
Are they also some Beyonder power?
Mr. Fool. I have successfully reached
a trade agreement with this gentleman.
Please allow me to make a presumptuous request.
Could you bear witness to our trade?
It's no trouble at all.
Then would you mind arranging
a few more gatherings like this?
Gatherings?
Mr. Fool.
Your powers far exceed our imaginations.
But the lady of lofty stature and myself
may be able to help you
achieve something trivial
that had previously inconvenienced you.
With more frequent gatherings
comes the risk of exposing myself.
But the more contact I have
with this mysterious realm.
the better my chances are
of finding a way home.
I must overcome this fear of the unknown.
Then let us meet every Monday
at three in the afternoon.
Try your best to be alone.
You may continue.
Shall we give ourselves code names. then?
After all. we can't use our
real names for conversation.
Good idea.
Since Mr. Fool's name is derived
from the tarot...
I know! I shall be Justice!
Audrey Hall
Justice. Tarot Club
The Hanged Man.
Alger Wilson
The Hanged Man. Tarot Club
Then that makes us the founding
members of the Tarot Club!
I'm losing strength...
I heard that initially.
Emperor Roselle made a
different deck of tarot cards.
Yes.
It is said that Emperor Roselle
had seen the Blasphemy Slate
which contains the profound mysteries
of the 22 Paths of the Divine.
Enough.
Today's gathering ends here.
By your will.
Who is it?
The police.
Coming.
An inspector?
Apologies. I was just having a nap.
We meet again.
You're the guy... who was
following me in the town square.
"Following" you?
Leonard Mitchell
Loen Kingdom. Awwa County Police
An interesting choice of words.
Why can't I have been "protecting" you?
Leonard Mitchell. Awwa County Police.
You're entering without—
Relax. Mr. Moretti.
We just want to ask you a few questions.
Dunn Smith
Loen Kingdom. Awwa County Police
Inspectors...
Did Naya and Welch really...
take their own lives?
Judging from the scene. yes.
You call that suicide?
They looked possessed!
What "strange things"?
You...
And this here...
"Everyone will die. including me."
What did you mean by that?
I have no idea.
I really can't remember.
Especially recent events.
Evidence indicates that on the 27th.
you visited Mr. McGovern's residence.
So I did go there?
You might not believe what I'm saying.
but I can only guess at recent events
through reading my diary.
Mr. McGovern has lost a revolver.
I'd wager I should be able to find it here.
Isn't that right. Mr. Moretti?
It's in the stove over there.
Do you have anything you wish to add?
Yes.
Yesterday. I awoke in the middle of the night
and found myself collapsed over the desk.
as if I had gone through a failed suicide attempt.
After that.
I started to lose some memories.
Your mental fortitude is impressive.
You can tell from my voice I'm not lying. right?
That does fit what I've surmised so far.
However.
what I think is irrelevant.
You will have to pass a psychic test
administered by an expert.
She...
should be able to help you
recall your lost memories.
A psychic expert?
What if my memories of Earth are exposed?
You're a lucky one.
Frankly. we're relieved
to see you're still alive.
Usually. when we investigate a case like this one.
all involved parties...
are found dead.
What's wrong. Mr. Moretti?
If they find out that I'm a transmigrator...
Stop right there!
Damn it!
You rascal! You steal from me every day!
Stop right there!
Stop him!
Lemme go!
I've finally caught you.
Just have him return what he stole.
Let go of me. or I'll curse you!
This is my chance!
Let go!
Time and space are frozen?
It's a Beyonder!
To the pier outside the city.
You got it.
No one is coming after me
and there are no abnormalities.
Please pull over.
Where are you going?
To Welch's residence.
It was a dream?
When did I fall asleep?
Allow me to reintroduce myself.
Dunn Smith
Evernight Goddess. Nighthawk
Nighthawk.
Dunn Smith.
Was he the one manipulating my dream?
Is he a Beyonder?
Mr. Moretti.
In the dark of the night.
we are far more powerful than you can imagine.
"We"?
No need to be nervous.
I'll make you all slick and pliable.
so that you can open right up.
Don't...
Don't worry.
This is her idea of calming you down.
She prefers corpses over men.
Mom! Dad!
Klein.
Memories on the surface can be wiped away.
but in the vast ocean of the mind. there are
always shadows left drifting in the deep.
Did she see that?
No. she doesn't know yet.
Judging by her words. this is my mind.
and yet she can't see through to my secrets.
Could it be because of that gray fog?
Klein.
Tell me.
What did you do with the notebook
of the Antigonus Family?
The notebook is gone?
I don't know.
On June 27th.
what happened in Welch's home?
Welch...
Naya...
I don't know.
When they died.
what were you doing?
I...
I've... passed the test?
I can confirm three things.
He attempted suicide via gunshot.
but it's clear that he still lives.
As for his lost memories.
they are just like Welch and Naya's souls:
no trace remains.
I fear whatever power was able to affect him so.
Daly Simone
Evernight Goddess.
Nighthawk
I've never encountered something so troublesome.
You need to be careful.
The Antigonus Family's notebook is missing.
The threat to your life still remains.
Then I—
We're not your babysitters.
We can't always protect you.
Or...
Perhaps you'd like to join us and become...
a Beyonder?